Charles Lee Remington Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1936-2007; Series I
  - Salmon, John T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1956; 001080
  - Samuelson, G. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976; 001081
  - Sanderson, Milton W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1944-1972; 001082
  - Sargent, Theodore D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968-1975; 001083
  - Sbordoni, Valerio. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 001084
  - Schaefer, Carl W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985; 001085
  - Schaefer, Paul E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1968; 001086
  - Scheffler, Harold &. Anne W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 001087
  - Schlinger, Evert I. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1966; 001088
  - Schmidt, Karl P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 001089
  - Schrimer, George F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001090
  - Schroeter, Otto H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1950-1957; 001091
  - Schubert, Bernice G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1947; 001092
  - Schultz, Thomas David. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985-1988; 001093
  - Schunke, Jose M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 001094
  - Schuster, Rudolf M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 001095
  - Schwanwitsch, B. N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1959; 001096
  - Schwartz, Gail. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 001097
  - Schwartz, Ralph. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 001098
  - Schweitzer, Dale F. Est. number items = 21-50., 1975-1997; 001099
  - Scott, James. Est. number items = 11-20., 1965-1980; 001100
  - Scott, Michelle P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1990; 001101
  - Scott, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 001102
  - Scriber, J. Mark. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 001103
  - Scudder, G. G. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 001104
  - Seaborg, David M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 001105
  - Seeley, Thomas Dyer. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985; 001106
  - Seevers, Charlie H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945-1957; 001107
  - Seibert, Ray P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1959; 001108
  - Seifert, Richard P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001109
  - Sener, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 001110
  - Sergeev, Michael G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1990-1992; 001111
  - Seydel, Charles. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1958; 001112
  - Shapiro, Arthur M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1973; 001113
  - Shapley, Harlow. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 001114
  - Sharov, A. G. Est. number items = 11-20., 1958-1959; 001115
  - Shaw, Frank R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1957; 001116
  - Shaw, James H. Est. number items = 11-20., 1971-1982; 001117
  - Shay, W. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1930; 001118
  - Sheljuzhko, Leo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 001119
  - Shepherd, Roy F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001120
  - Sheppard, Philip M. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1961; 001121
  - Sherk, Truman. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1988; 001122
  - Sherman, John D. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943-1948; 001123
  - Shields, James E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1950; 001124
  - Shields, Oakley. Est. number items = 11-20., 1961-1990; 001125
  - Shirouz, Takashi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1956; 001126
  - Shoumatoff, Nicholas. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1963; 001127
  - Shulgin, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 001128
  - Shull, Ernest M. Est. number items = 5., 1959-1962; 002792
  - Sibley, George. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 001129
  - Sicher, Harry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1962; 001130
  - Sieker, William E. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1978; 001131
  - Silberglied, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1980; 001132
  - Silliman, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 001133
  - Silvestri, Filippo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1948; 001134
  - Simmons, Robert S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956-1963; 001135
  - Simon, David. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 001136
  - Singer, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 001137
  - Sinnott, Edmund H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1954; 001138
  - Slade, Jennifer. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1975; 001139
  - Slater, James A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1985; 001140
  - Smalley, Stephen B. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1975; 001141
  - Smallwood, William Henry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 001142
  - Smelhaus, Jiri. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 001143
  - Smith, Allyn G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1920; 001144
  - Smith, Audrey. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1961; 001145
  - Smith, David M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 001146
  - Smith, Kenneth G. V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1981; 001147
  - Smith, Kenneth M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1954; 001148
  - Smith, Leslie M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1960; 001149
  - Smith, M. Eugene. Est. number items = 1-10., 1936-1947; 001150
  - Smith, Marion E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1962; 001151
  - Smith, Ray F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1963; 001152
  - Smith, Richard S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1987; 001153
  - Smith, Stanley G. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1965; 001154
  - Smith, T. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001155
  - Smith, Vick T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1954; 001156
  - Smulders, Francis. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 001157
  - Snapp, Oliver I. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 001158
  - Snodgrass, R. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1947; 001159
  - Snyder, Lee R. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 001160
  - Sokal, Robert R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965-1967; 001161
  - Sollaart, A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001162
  - Sommerman, Kathryn M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1963; 001163
  - Spackman, William Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 001164
  - Spector, Willian S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001165
  - Spencer, G. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 001166
  - Spencer, John C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001167
  - Sperling, Felix. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 001168
  - Speyer, W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1956; 001169
  - Spieth, Herman T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 001170
  - Sprugel, George Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1971; 001171
  - Stadler, Joan. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 001172
  - Staid, J. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924-1925; 001173
  - Stallings, Donald Briggs (incl. J. R. E. Turner). Est. number items = 50+., 1942-1988; 001174
  - Stanfield, J. Fisher. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1957; 001175
  - Stanford, Ray E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1976; 001176
  - Stange, Lionel A. Est. number items = 2., 002793
  - Stannard, Lewis J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1952; 001177
  - Starrett, Andrew. Est. number items = 11-20., 1957-1972; 001178
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1966; 001179
  - Stein, Robert C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1964-1970; 001180
  - Steinhaus, Edward A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001181
  - Sternitzky, R. F. Est. number items = 50+., 1932-1974; 001182
  - Stone, Alan. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1966; 001183
  - Strandtmann, R. W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1946-1979; 001184
  - Strange, Lionel A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 001185
  - Sturtevant, A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001186
  - Suomalainen, Esko. Est. number items = 11-20., 1951-1969; 001187
  - Sussman, Alfred S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1951; 001188
  - Suzuki, Kunio. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 001189
  - Sweadner, Walter R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1956; 001190
  - Sweetman, Harvey L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1949; 001191
  - Swingen, John L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 001192
  - Symmes, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001193
  - Szent-Ivany, J. J. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 001194
  - Takahasi, Hirosi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1988; 001195
  - Tatewaki, M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1966; 001196
  - Taylor, Orley R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1969; 001197
  - Taylor, Paul. Est. number items = 11-20., 1978-1981; 001198
  - Theodor, Oscar. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980-1981; 001199
  - Thien, Leonard B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1982; 001200
  - Thomas, Edward S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 001201
  - Thorne, Fred. Est. number items = 50+., 1950-1973; 001202
  - Tieges, O. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1956; 001203
  - Tietz, Harrison M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 001204
  - Tilden, J. William. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1961; 001205
  - Tinbergen, Niko. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001206
  - Todd, Edward. Est. number items = 1-10., 1940-1943; 001207
  - Toft, Catherine A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1982; 001208
  - Tolis, George Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 001209
  - Tomita, G. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 001210
  - Tomlin, V. R. W. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945; 001211
  - Torrey, Theodore W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 001212
  - Toshima, Hiromu. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1964; 001213
  - Townes, Abner A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 001214
  - Townes, Henry. Est. number items = 11-20., 1935-1974; 001215
  - Treat, Asher E. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1962; 001216
  - Tremewan, W. Gerald. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001217
  - Tripp, Howard A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001218
  - Troxell, Edward L. Est. number items = 21-50., 1950-1952; 001219
  - Tsuruta, Ts. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001220
  - Tugendhot, Trixie. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001221
  - Turner, Frederick B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001222
  - Turner, John R. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1985; 001223
  - Turner, Nealy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1957; 001224
  - Turner, Ruth D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 001225
  - Turner, Ted. Est. number items = 1-10., 1995; 001226
  - Turner, William J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1982; 001227
  - Tuxen, S. L. Est. number items = 21-50., 1958-1969; 001228
  - Uchida, Hajime. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1963; 001229
  - Udvardy, Miklos D. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 001230
  - Upton, Murray. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001231
  - Urbano, Robert F. Est. number items = 5., 1971; 002794
  - Urquhart, Fred A. Est. number items = 11-20., 1943-1978; 001232
  - Usinger, Robert L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1948; 001233
  - Utterback, W. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 001234
  - Vaccaro, Francesco. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 001235
  - Valentine, J. Manson. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001236
  - Valletta, Anthony. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001237
  - Van Hyning, T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 001238
  - Vanek, Jaroslav. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1982; 001241
  - Varley, George C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1970; 001242
  - Vars, William. Est. number items = 11-20., 1978-2000; 001243
  - Vermeij, Geerat J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 001244
  - Vessels, Robert D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1951; 001245
  - Viette, Pierre E. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1954; 001246
  - Vieu, Rene. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1963; 001247
  - Vishniac, Roman. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1967; 001248
  - Vogel, Beatrice. Est. number items = 11., 1962-1964; 002795
  - Wage, Jeff. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1982; 001250
  - Wagner, David L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986-1994; 001251
  - Wagner, Warren Herbert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1942-1980; 001252
  - Waldbauer, Gilbert P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1980; 001253
  - Waldner, Raymond E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989-1990; 001254
  - Walker, Bryant. Est. number items = 11-20., 1924-1928; 001255
  - Wall, William Jr. J. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1962; 001256
  - Wallace, Bruce. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1960; 001257
  - Walsten, David M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 001258
  - Walter, Laurie R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1985; 001259
  - Wanmaker, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 001260
  - Ware, Agnes &. Richard C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974; 001261
  - Warnecke, Georg. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 001262
  - Warren, B. C. S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1951-1963; 001263
  - Watanabe, C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1958; 001264
  - Waterhouse, D. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1978; 001265
  - Waterman, Tal H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1956; 001266
  - Watson, J. A. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 001267
  - Watt, Alice. Est. number items = 1., 1977; 002796
  - Watt, Laura. Est. number items = 3., 1991; 002797
  - Watt, Ward A. Est. number items = 50+., 1955-1993; 001268
  - Weast, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1961; 001269
  - Webb, Glenn R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 001270
  - Webb, Walter F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 001271
  - Weber, Bernard H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980-1982; 001272
  - Weber, Neal A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 001273
  - Weeks, W. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923; 001274
  - Weems, Howard V. Est. number items = 11-20., 1960-1986; 001275
  - Wehr, Wesley. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 001276
  - Weintraub, Jason. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1978; 001277
  - Weissman, David. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1983; 001278
  - Weld, Lewis H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 001279
  - Welling, Eduardo C. Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1984; 001280
  - Wells, Patrick H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 001281
  - Wells, Stephen R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 001282
  - Wenner, Adrian M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1972; 001283
  - Wenzel, Rupert L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1972; 001284
  - Werner, Floyd G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1945-1958; 001285
  - West, David A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1986; 001286
  - Westing, Arthur H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 001287
  - Wetzler, Richard E. Est. number items = 11-20., 1975-1986; 001288
  - Wharton, G. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1953; 001289
  - Wheat, Pat. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1986; 001290
  - Wheeler, H. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 001291
  - White, C. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923; 001292
  - White, Harold B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 001293
  - Whitecomb, Walter F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1935; 001294
  - Whitehead, Paul F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1983-1991; 001295
  - Whiteney, George D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1996; 001296
  - Whittaker, Robert H. Est. number items = 11-20., 1939-1966; 001297
  - Wiest, Roy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 001298
  - Wilcke, H. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1955; 001299
  - Wilcox, A. M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1917-1918; 001300
  - Wilcox, Bruce. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975-1980; 001301
  - Wilhelm, Herman P. Est. number items = 50+., 1949-1966; 001302
  - Wilkinson, Ronald S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976; 001303
  - Willette, Robert E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 001304
  - Williams, C. B. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1958; 001305
  - Williams, Carroll M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1972; 001306
  - Williams, E. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 001307
  - Williams, Jorge V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001308
  - Williamson, E. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 001309
  - Willnick, A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1958; 001310
  - Wilson, C. Eric. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1958; 001311
  - Wilson, Edward O. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1982; 001312
  - Wilson, F. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943-1953; 001313
  - Wilson, Kent H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1950-1978; 001314
  - Wilson, William J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 001315
  - Wiltshire, E. P. Est. number items = 11-20., 1956-1959; 001316
  - Wind, Robert G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1955-1971; 001317
  - Witmer, Rudolf H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 001318
  - Witner, William D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976-1996; 001319
  - Witz, Adolf. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1954; 001320
  - Woglum, Russell S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 001321
  - Womersley, H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 001322
  - Wood, Carroll E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1978; 001323
  - Woodcock, H. E. Est. number items = 21-50., 1939-1953; 001324
  - Woodhouse, L. G. O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1960; 001325
  - Woodland, John T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1958; 001326
  - Woodward, Jessie B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 001327
  - Worth, C. Brooke. Est. number items = 1-10., 001328
  - Wright, Amy Bartlett. Est. number items = 1-10., 1990; 001329
  - Wright, David M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 001330
  - Wyatt, Alex K. Est. number items = 21-50., 1942-1958; 001331
  - Wyatt, Colin W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 001332
  - Wygodzinsky, Pedro W. Est. number items = 50+., 1946-1961; 001333
  - Young, Allen M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1973; 001334
  - Young, Elwood P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 001335
  - Young, Frank N. Est. number items = 11-20., 1937-1985; 001336
  - Zachler, Friedrich. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 001337
  - Zalucki, M. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 001338
  - Zeiger, Charles F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1965; 001339
  - Zetek, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1920-1925; 001340
  - Ziegler, J. Benjamin. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1974; 001341
  - Zimmerman, Elwood C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1980; 001342
  - Zinn, Donald J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1991; 001343
  - Zischka, Rudolf. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 001344
  - Zweifel, Richard G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 001345
  - da Silva, Laura Atilde C. Malheiro. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000306
  - de Fluiter, H. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000327
  - de Lesse, H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000330
  - de Terra, Helmut. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000331
  - de Wyngaert, Ch. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000332
  - de la Torre y Callejas, Salvador L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1958; 000328
  - de la Torre-Bueno, J. R. Est. number items = 11-20., 1942-1949; 000329
  - dos Passos, Cyril F. Est. number items = 50+., 1936-1973; 000366
  - du Pont, Dorothy L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976-1978; 000381
  - van Someren, V. G. L. Est. number items = 24., 1954-1965; 001239
  - van Son, G. Est. number items = 11., 1954-1958; 001240
  - von Froreich. Est. number items = 3., 1960; 001249
- Yale College Course Materials, Series II
  All of his course materials.
  - Associated Courses. Associated courses & seminars in which Charles Lee Remington attended & gave guest lectures etc. EST number items = 15., 001380
  - BIO 11. College course material from BIO 11; Intro to Biology. Est. number items 50+., 1951-1976; 001346
  - BIO 121b. Yale College course material for BIO 121b. EST number items =100+ pgs., 1980-1991; 001352
  - BIO 122b. Yale College course material for BIO 122b, Biogeography. EST number items =10-20., 001353
  - BIO 128. College course material from BIO 128. EST number items = 5., 1942; 001361
  - BIO 20b. College course material from BIO 20b; Natural History. Syllabus and course review. number items 4., 1951-1964; 001347
  - BIO 218. Yale College course material for BIO 218, Biogeography. EST number items =100+., 1977-1988; 001354
  - BIO 220. Yale College course material for Bio 220., 1989-1992; 001355
  - BIO 221. College course material from BIO 221. EST number items = 13., 1991-1992; 001362
  - BIO 242b. Yale College course material for BIO 242b. EST number items = 50+., 1979-1988; 001356
  - BIO 244b. Yale College course material for BIO 244b, Biogeography. EST number items =30+., 1983; 001357
  - BIO 366. Yale College course material for BIO 366. Also see BIO 36. EST number items =200+., 1969-1979; 001358
  - BIO 36b. College course material from BIO 36b. Also see BIO366. EST number items = 50., 1969-1980; 001348
  - BIO 41b-341b. College course material from BIO 41b - 341b. EST number items = 1-10., 1967-1968; 001349
  - BIO 42b - 342b. College course material from BIO 42b - 342b. EST number items = 25+., 1969-1975; 001350
  - BIO 51a - 51b. EST number items = 8 packets, 100+ pgs., 1962-1969; 001351
  - BIO 671. College course material from BIO 671, some course work if shared with GEO 164. EST number items = 60+., 1962-1965; 001360
  - BIO375. College course material from BIO 375. EST number items = 200+., 1966-1976; 001359
  - CLR Course Notes. Notes hand written by Charles Lee Remington mostly on insect morphology and physiology. EST number items = 100., 001383
  - CSPC 31a. College course material from CSPC 31a. EST number items = 20+., 1973-1974; 001376
  - Cronon Seminar. Documents pertaining to the Cronon Seminars, Now called ISPS. EST number items =50+., 001381
  - FES 504. College course material from FES 504. EST number items = 50+., 1993-1998; 001363
  - FES 520. College course material from FES 520. EST number items = 10., 1992; 001364
  - FES 557. College course material from FES 557. EST number items = 60+., 1983-1999; 001365
  - FES 562. College course material from FES 562. EST number items = 100+., 1991-1999; 001366
  - FES 574. College course material from FES 574, shared some course materials with BIO 375. EST number items = 30-50., 1980-1988; 001367
  - FES 581. College course material from FES 581; Museology. EST number items = 50+., 1985-1997; 001368
  - GEO 717. College course material from GEO 711, also associated with BIO 826. EST number items = 40+., 1980-1981; 001377
  - Lecture Slides. Master list of lecture slides used in Charles Lee Remingtons Yale courses., 001378
  - Master Handouts. Master Handouts used for many Yale courses tought by Charles Lee Remington. EST number items = 150+., 001379
  - Peabody Centenial., 001427
  - ZOO 120. College course material from ZOO 120. Number items = 7., 1949-1954; 001371
  - ZOO 131. College course material from ZOO 131. Number items = 6., 1952-1955; 001372
  - ZOO 160. College course material from ZOO 160. Number items = 17., 001373
  - ZOO 164. College course material from ZOO 164. Number items = 200+., 1950-1962; 001374
  - ZOO 39b. College course material from ZOO 39b. EST number items = 50+., 1956-1962; 001369
  - ZOO 44a. College course material from ZOO 44a, some course work is shared with BIO 11. EST number items = 20+., 1959-1961; 001370
  - ZOO 44b. College course material from ZOO 44b. Number items = 6., 1964; 001375
  - Zoology Journal Clubs. Zoology Journal Club records. EST number items =30+., 1949-1960; 001382
- Lecture & Research Trips, 1939-2007; Series III
  Documents pertaining to trips taken by Charles Lee Remington for lecture and research purpose's.
  - 1939-1944. EST number of items = 1-10., 001387
  - 1945-1949. EST number of items = 25+., 001388
  - 1950-1954. EST number of items = 25+., 001389
  - 1955-1959. EST number of items = 50+., 001390
  - 1960-1967. EST number of items = 25+., 001391
  - 1968-1969. EST number of items = 40+., 001392
  - 1970-1972. EST number of items = 50+., 001393
  - 1973-1976. EST number of items = 40+., 001394
  - 1977-1979. EST number of items = 40+., 001395
  - 1980-1982. EST number of items = 40+., 001396
  - 1983-1986. EST number of items = 25+., 001397
  - 1987-1989. EST number of items = 25+., 001398
  - 1990-1992. EST number of items = 25+. Charles Lee Remington's retirement information is included., 001399
  - 1993-1995. Number of items = 5. 1 item is a folder containing about 10 items., 001400
  - 1996-2001. EST number of items =1-10., 001401
  - Collecting Permits. Collecting peremits for Charles Lee Remmington for various trips. EST number of items = 30+., 001757
  - Summary Lists. EST number of items = 30+., 001385
- Newspaper Clippings, Series IV
  News paper clippings of Charles Lee Remington including Yale newsletters and radio show outlines.
  - Articles of Interest. Miscellaneous newspaper clippings saved by Charles Lee Remington which do not feature him. Some are of colleagues, others just topics of intereast to CLR., 001749
  - Butterflies. Newspaper clippings on Charles lee Remingtons work with Burtterflies., 001746